(Lee Yoon Seo)
(Day One)
Where are you going?
The restroom.
So...
Someone will come to the retreat
center in the morning, right?
If no one comes for us,
let's just leave.
(You must follow the rules of Mafia.)
(If you don't execute one
of the players until 6am, )
(one of you will be executed instead.)
Oh, no.
It's 6am now.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey, stop that!
If we don't kill anyone,
we'll be the ones who die.
Oh, no.
- Let's hurry up and go.
- Jun Hee.
Just a second.
- Wait. No!
- Hey!
Let go of me.
No.
It's your fault.
This is all your fault.
You must follow the rules of Mafia.
You must hold a meeting...
to come to a unanimous decision
on the player you will execute.
(You must follow the rules of Mafia.)
(You must hold a meeting...)
(to come to a unanimous decision
on the player you will execute.)
(Lee Yoon Seo)
I should have at least told him.
That I had feelings for him.
That I really...
liked him.
Before the last vote closed,
the Doctor nominated whom to Heal.
The nominated player was Kim Jun Hee.
Thanks to Doctor's ability to Heal,
Kim Jun Hee has been brought back to life.
Are you okay?
What a relief.
I'm so relieved.
I was really scared.
I'm so relieved you're back.
Gosh. How does this make sense?
The class president came back?
Even a Doctor...
Hey.
Kim Jin Ha?
During the night, Shin Seung Bin...
was executed by the Mafia.
- Hey. Kim Jin Ha!
- Shin Seung Bin was...
a Citizen.
Morning has come.
- You startled me.
- What's going on?
- Why did you take off your shirt?
- Identify the Mafia...
and begin to vote.
Where did the blood come from?
Whose blood is it?
It's nothing.
What's going on?
What was that? Wasn't that blood?
I'm certain it was blood. Right?
- What's going on?
- It was blood.
Jun Hee!
I was so scared that you were really dead.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
Did you see the photo from yesterday?
The photo Yoon Seo had.
What?
You threw it out here yesterday, right?
She's driving me crazy.
Do you still believe her?
You died because of her. Get a grip!
- Kim So Mi.
- You know I'm right.
Am I wrong?
Goodness!
Hey!
Did you kill him?
It wasn't me. I didn't kill him!
When I woke up this morning,
that's how I found him.
It wasn't me.
Guys, it really wasn't me.
Hey, Yoon Seo.
The three of them were inseparable.
Talk about some loyal friends.
Let's go. The smell of the
blood makes me want to puke.
Seung Bin...
was stabbed a lot of times by a knife.
Why take things that far?
Don't talk about that.
No one wants to know.
This is morbid.
I think he was stabbed
even after he had died.
The Mafia didn't take things
far with the other kids.
But this time,
I get the feeling the Mafia
really wanted him dead.
Seung Bin was dead in a pool of blood.
Then my body was covered in blood.
I was so shocked.
It really wasn't you?
No!
It looked like they were
suspecting me, right?
Yes.
Darn it. Come on, Seung Bin. That jerk.
Why did he have to die when he was with me?
Kyung Jun.
Can you tell them that
I'm not the Mafia? Please?
They listen to you.
You said we should have each other's back.
Okay.
Thank you, Kyung Jun. I'll
really be good to you.
(Jun Hee is a Citizen. From Police)
Hey, did you write that down?
It wasn't me.
What's this?
Did the Police really write this?
It wasn't here yesterday, right?
No. I don't remember seeing it.
(Police)
- It wasn't me.
- Who wrote that?
Who on earth are the Police?
- Is it you?
- You think?
I had no choice but to lie yesterday.
I'm a Citizen.
I don't know who the Doctor is.
Thank you.
Hey, you coming back to
life is a separate matter.
We can't be sure if
you're a Citizen or not.
Right.
How come his identity
wasn't revealed yesterday?
The identities are usually
revealed when they die.
It wasn't revealed because
he wasn't out of the game.
It really wasn't you who
wrote the message on the wall?
I didn't.
It's not like I had time to write that.
You probably wrote that in
the middle of the night.
Hey.
Why would he lie to us that he
was the Mafia unless he was crazy?
Let's just vote him out.
Hey, he's a Citizen.
What would you do if the
Police really wrote that?
Right.
The Doctor might have saved Jun
Hee, knowing he was a Citizen.
Isn't finding the person...
who killed Seung Bin a
more pressing matter...
than interrogating Jun Hee?
It wasn't me.
When I woke up, I found him dead.
You said it was just you and him. Right?
Did you see anything unusual?
I don't know.
The Mafia put blood on me on
purpose when I was asleep.
Right, Kyung Jun?
You know that I'm a Citizen. Right?
How would I know that?
What?
You came out, covered in blood.
That's evidence.
Seung Bin kept picking on you.
You got angry. Isn't that why you did it?
Hey, you're suspecting Jin Ha too.
Let's just vote him out.
How could you call yourself
a friend, you jerk?
You darn Mafia. You must have a death wish.
You scumbag.
- Hey.
- Move! Darn it.
Vote him out now!
Hey. You don't know that for sure.
Shut your mouth, and just do it.
Give it back.
You'll keep doing whatever you want?
Darn you. Just give back my phone.
If you keep this up,
you might end up getting all the votes.
Let's reconvene at 11pm.
Let's not vote until then.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Kim So Mi.
Can we talk?
Guys.
It really wasn't me. Don't vote me out.
I'll find out who killed Seung Bin.
You just wait.
Do you think Jin Ha killed him?
He must have known we'd suspect
him because of the blood.
He has no reason to do that.
Exactly.
Then he should've told us.
Why would he run away?
That makes him look suspicious.
By the way, Ko Kyung Jun is unbelievable.
He abandoned Kim Jin Ha right away.
Seriously...
Those backstabbing jerks.
Considering his actions,
Ko Kyung Jun is the Mafia.
(Jun Hee is a Citizen. From Police)
Guys.
If the police wrote this,
why wrote only Jun Hee?
The skill was used twice.
There must be more than one.
Maybe it's written somewhere else.
He should've written who the Mafia is.
Don't frame Yoon Seo or anyone else for me.
Jun Hee, I was only trying to save you.
I was trying to help you.
I never asked for your help.
Don't blame me.
You did it for yourself.
Kim Jun Hee.
Don't you remember what I did for you?
Who sided with you when you were suspected?
It was me!
Hey.
Get a hold of yourself.
Do you want me to consider you a Mafia?
Suit yourself.
Yu Jun.
Eat even if you don't want to.
You haven't eaten anything.
(Jin Da Bum)
My laptop is in the basement.
Oh, right.
I'll go with you.
(Lee Yoon Seo)
Watch.
They didn't move.
Isn't that strange?
- Watch.
- What's that?
How is that possible?
I know.
- Let me see.
- Okay.
One sec.
Yoon Seo.
Dang it. Who was it?
I didn't notice anything strange.
When I ran yesterday,
Hey, what about us?
If we stay together, it's more dangerous.
Where are we supposed to go?
Go to the arcade.
Only Ko Kyung Jun knew...
we were hiding in here.
How come you didn't go with Kim Jun Hee?
Don't talk to me about him anymore.
Na Hee, you done eating?
Let's go.
So sensitive. What's her problem?
She was fighting with Kim Jun Hee earlier.
Do they have issues?
If you're done, leave.
I haven't eaten yet.
Don't you know a break time?
It's closed.
Give me a break.
What's his deal now?
Close the door behind you.
(Find the game host.)
Host?
Yoon Seo.
What are you doing?
It's doing the same thing.
What do you mean?
I mean,
when I just took pictures, it was fine.
But only our faces look weird.
Just like that group photo.
What's wrong?
I saw a ghost earlier.
And I found this.
What's that key for?
I don't know what it's for,
but if there's a message for it,
It must be something important.
What message?
To find a host.
Didn't you get it?
(No new messages)
No, I didn't get any.
What about you?
Not for me.
Me too. I didn't get any.
What?
Was it just me?
What did it say? Show me.
It disappeared.
Anyway, there must be a
reason to find a host.
Let's tell everyone and search together.
Do we have to tell them now?
To be honest, I don't know
what you're talking about.
When we went to the swimming pool
yesterday, we didn't find anything.
What if you get suspected as a Mafia...
for saying that?
This has nothing to do with Mafia.
I even got a message.
You said it disappeared.
If other people don't believe
it, there's nothing you can do.
You don't trust me either.
It's not that we don't trust you.
That's what the situation says.
Right.
I was saying, we should be careful...
until we find solid evidence.
Yoon Seo, I trust you.
But Jung Won also has a point.
Let's not make other people anxious...
and keep it between us for now.
Okay.
Do you want me to find the
album the photo was in?
The game must take place
within the boundaries.
(Workroom)
Darn you, Ko Kyung Jun.
I wondered who was following me.
That rat was you.
Darn jerk.
You hid an ax.
What's this?
What the heck is that?
Were you going to burn it
to get rid of evidence?
It really was you.
You killed Shin Seung Bin!
I was framed too!
Framed for what?
You tried to frame me.
You crazy Mafia.
Do you still call yourself a human?
- Darn you.
- Shoot.
Let it go.
- You jerk.
- Let it go.
You Mafia.
You prick.
Come here, you punk.
- Let me go, you jerks.
- Come here.
Let me go.
Let go of me, you Mafia jerks.
Dang it.
You killed Shin Seung Bin and Ji Soo...
You killed Ji Soo too!
It wasn't me.
Guys!
- Ko Kyung Jun and...
- Be quiet!
Stop him.
(Check for safety before work.
Clean up after work.)
Shoot.
Why did you have to push him?
Why didn't you hold him tight?
Hey.
What are you going to do?
If he tells everyone,
we're doomed.
Do you think they'll buy us?
What are you doing?
Kill him.
Gosh.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through
Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform
Content Production Business.)